Nor not down like capping...
...called bleeding love...grammy nominations
...became the best selling single worldwide that...twenty-eight that
...year she became the first british female solo artist to top the us billboard
tudor chart more than twenty years with her debut album the called spirit her career started
back in twenty-fifth when she took the crown on the third...uk x factor.
The decades later she stepping onto a broadly
...for the first time the revival of andrew lloyd webber tony-winning classic cats
...signatures song...called memory accords leona lewis
...at the table hello momoa.
Budgeting I went to the show on saturday when you think that
...goosebumps everybody would on their feet at that particular moment no-go you but you
...dot...you said when you were...seven a new thought what when you heard the
accountability original production in london and my mom put me today
...it...magical at the may lagging and,
not songs in particulate stuck in my head and alive of michigan thing
...nine and the guy thing in...in hacked london
...and unit thing and my little baby boy...momoa.
Composer andrew lloyd webber dead that you have one of the greatest voices of
your generation...the world
Incredible.
Figure black moi.
...the at the night
...that the fact...get become heron and perform momoa.
...expected mean to you...they, yeah, they act that...kind
...all began and ultimately the other day content when...you
cheat that blowing up the...get...on...which took care...whole new that but
within just in the uk anymore with worldwide though it was
all around that time and gave me a huge platform now I heard that everybody on stage
has to do their own make-up yet because there's so many so you get a let them
...how-to-do-it and you have to do-it-yourself yet...help the to do and
...night we have to trumbull knocked off into the cat will about getting into the character in the
...that the get trampling from the human and that...been a couple days pretending to be
a cat what...out...I mean when we fat gaa...never
ran for the beagle you've never met before and the directive...heck looked looking at like
cut the day and we would just like cooling...like...the...like...a ball-like
...it yet...we...got nature the real quick that...even like cap
I day add-on actually and have an animal sanctuary in the uk and,
we have lots of cats the animal sanctuary...you musical great
...ignoring our singing bleeding love because we both...really,
really like your music and that...all get better we'll all be better in time
...people play I've heard people say many done that actually...them allergic to that
...I'm not...that too, yeah, I have a lot of them reaction
...particular and it co-chair
...it that poignant it will get better in time...the...you do
...and you can apply it...relationship you can applied to a traumatic
...and in your life your job as?
...the and...in london and convicted
...I'll and yet but then you come the new york to do...
new here and it quite...london actually,
you know, ...the people using the subway and getting on the bopped it but
...very it's got very london by the ballad...climbing...get along now,
you know, they were report that...had a little crippled yet what relationship like
my son interrogated always been good he...during the x
factor and,...what to him the seven years that...I decided
to ...labeled that I think that...decided to do that people like...
happened but it...good...memory your favorite...cat...I want them I
love and gus the theatre cat and...ready great number
...memory...and captive playing now on broadway you're watching...like that.